Guide to the Lesbian and Gay Liberation Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Additional material, 1948-2010; Accession 2012-M-030
  - Musical concerts, performances, and dances, 1977-2006
    - "Rites of Spring" [program], Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "Romanovsky and Phillips in Concert" [flyer], 1985 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - "San Francisco Conservatory of Music: At the Conservatory" [pamphlet], 1997 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "San Francisco Gay Men's Chorus Tours America '81" [program], 1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "San Francisco Gay Men's Chorus: Ten Proud Years" [program], 1988 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "San Francisco Gay Men's Chorus: Thank You for the Music" [program], 2006 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "San Francisco Gay Men's Chorus In Concert" [program], 1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "San Francisco Gay Men's Chorus and the San Francisco Lesbian and Gay Men's Community Chorus Spring 1982 Concert Series" [pamphlet] (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "San Francisco Gay Men's Chorus: Presenting the Classics" [program], 1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "San Francisco Gay Men's Chorus In Concert" [program], Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "San Francisco Gay Men's Chorus: Now Sing with Hearts Aglow" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "San Francisco Gay Men's Chorus 24th Subscription Season" [pamphlet], 2001-2002 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "San Francisco Lesbian Chorus and the LA Women's Community Chorus" [flyer], 1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "San Francisco Lesbian/Gay Freedom Band: World Premier" [flyer], 2000 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "San Francisco Opera, The Rake's Progress, 1999-2000 Season" (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "San Francisco Winds of Freedom: Community Concert Series" [flyer], 1996 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Sawdust [flyer], 1983 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Shannon, Lori and Bergren, Lynda: Together Again for the Very First Time" [flyer], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Society of Gay and Lesbian Composers", 1987 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Solstice Dance and Music" [flyer], 1992 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Stockholms Gay Kor Go West" [program], 2006 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Stud [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Superband Concert" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Sweat: The New York - SF Gay Dance Inferno" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Sylvester, Fantasy Records, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - "Tatiana Presents 'Live at the Green Room'" [flyer], 1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "The Lesbian/Gay Chorus Goes to the Movies" [program], 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "The Valentine Divine: A Gala Tribute to Marilyn Monroe" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - This Is Our Country, Lesbian/Gay Chorus of San Francisco [program], 1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Tom Robinson Band" [press release], Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Too Much Fun, San Francisco Gay Men's Chorus [program], Circa 1981 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Trockadero de Monte Carlo" [flyer], 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Trull, Teresa and Band" [flyer], 1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Two Professional Acrobats and One Guy Just Fooling Around" [flyer], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Two Tons O' Fun" [flyer], 1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Tyler, Robin: Comedy Show" [flyer], 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Watch Me Shine: A musical History of the Gay and Lesbian Experience" [flyer], 2005 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Watkins, Mary: Something Moving" [pamphlet], Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "West Coast Choral Festival" [flyer], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Western Star Dancers" [pamphlet], 1999 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "West Coast Women's Music and Comedy Festival, Fourth Annual" [flyer], 1983 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "West Coast Women's Music Festival, Third Annual" [pamphlet], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "West Coast Women's Music Festival, Third Annual" [flyer], 1982 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Western Electric: A Mixed Country and Western Band" [flyer], Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Will and Grace: Let the Music Out! [flyer], 2004 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - "Women's Dance Party" [flyer], 1984 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - You Bet We Sing Love Songs, San Francisco Lesbian Chorus [program], Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - You and the Night and the Music [program], Circa 1988 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Yours in Sand, Taupe, Moss or Charoal, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Religion, 1969-1977
    - Blasphemy in Britain: The practice and punishment of blasphemy, and the trial of Gay News, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Sermonette: The radio inside us, "Sermon: The Christian Faith and Homosexuality," by Dale E. Turner, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - The Council on Religion and the Homosexual (pamphlet), Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Trends, "Homosexuality", 1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      This is Vol. 5, No. 6.
    - "United Church of Christ Resolution on Homosexuals and the Law", 1969 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Sports, 1976-2006 (Box 8, Folder 2-7)
  - Travel guides, 1974-2003
    - California - Los Angeles, Palm Springs, San Diego, 1988-1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - California - San Francisco, 1979-2001 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
    - Colorado, 1990-1996 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Florida, 1985-1990 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Illinois - Massachussetts, 1974-1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - New England - New York, 1989-1995 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Northeast - Pacific Northwest, 1980-1992 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania - Washington, 1987-1994 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Australia - Canada, 1981-1997 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - England - Zurich, 1976-2003 (Box 9, Folder 10)